<result>
	<partialresource>
		<resourceid>3</resourceid>
		<title>4Teachers</title>
		<description>helps teachers integrate technology into instruction. It features various tools for teachers: one for creating quizzes that students can take online, another for organizing and annotating web sites, a third for developing rubrics, and more. A webzine presents brain games, web lessons, and stories about teachers and students using technology.</description>
	</partialresource>
	<partialresource>
		<resourceid>318</resourceid>
		<title>The Whole Frog Project</title>
		<description>introduces the concepts of modern, computer based 3D visualization and demonstrates the power of whole body, 3D imaging of anatomy as a curriculum tool. A frog can be seen with or without its skeleton, brain, kidneys, etc., as the user desires, in cross-section slices, or in a rotating movie.</description>
	</partialresource>
	<partialresource>
		<resourceid>747</resourceid>
		<title>NIDA Goes to School</title>
		<description>contains brief guides and research reports on various drugs and the effects of drug abuse on the body and the brain. It also links to the journal, "NIDA Notes," and to five differently-organized NIDA search engines.</description>
	</partialresource>
	<partialresource>
		<resourceid>985</resourceid>
		<title>Beyond Discovery</title>
		<description>traces the origins of technological and medical advances. Learn about the genetics of ear wax, a vaccine to control malaria, DNA barcoding, aging and the human brain, a genetic classification of dog breeds, the discovery of the first "speech and language" gene, how living organisms tune in to the time of day, and more.</description>
	</partialresource>
	<partialresource>
		<resourceid>1311</resourceid>
		<title>The Secret Life of the Brain</title>
		<description>presents a history of efforts to understand the brain, a three-dimensional tour of the brain, optical illusions, and an animation showing how magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) works. Videoclips examine how the brain evolves and differs from infancy to childhood, adolescence, and through adulthood.</description>
	</partialresource>
	<partialresource>
		<resourceid>1370</resourceid>
		<title>Exploratorium Online</title>
		<description>features dozens of online learning activities and exhibits. Make a mold terrarium, pinhole projector, telescope, or hair hygrometer. Explore the brain, biodiversity, Antarctica, DNA, frogs, structures, or illusions. Learn about magnetism, electricity, motors, eyeballs, perception, Mars, chocolate, seasonings, or the science of cooking, sports, and music. Search over 3,000 photos and movies. Watch webcasts of science demonstrations by teachers.</description>
	</partialresource>
	<partialresource>
		<resourceid>1384</resourceid>
		<title>NIH Curriculum Supplement Series</title>
		<description>offers web-based instructional modules based on cutting-edge scientific discoveries. Topics include cell biology and cancer, infectious diseases, human genetic variation, sleep disorders, neurobiology and addiction, chemicals and the environment, alcohol, the brain and hearing, the mouth and tooth decay. Most modules are for middle and high school. Each includes inquiry-based activities and extensive background materials. Each was field tested by teachers.</description>
	</partialresource>
	<partialresource>
		<resourceid>1396</resourceid>
		<title>The Brain: Understanding Neurobiology Through the Study of Addiction</title>
		<description>helps students discover the fundamentals of neurobiology and how drugs change the brain. Among the topics: functions of specific brain areas; anatomy of the neuron; neurotransmission; drug action on neurons; genetic, behavioral, and environmental influences on drug addiction; and addiction as a chronic disease.</description>
	</partialresource>
	<partialresource>
		<resourceid>1557</resourceid>
		<title>NOVA scienceNOW</title>
		<description>is the companion website for a TV show on science breakthroughs and personalities. Learn about a frog that freezes solid in winter and comes back to life in spring. Watch videos about robot "swarms" that work together on a task, a newly discovered system in the brain, tools for predicting a hurricane's intensity, and why some sand dunes burp, sing, and croak. A teacher's guide and transcript are included. The show is hosted by Robert Krulwich and airs five times a year.</description>
	</partialresource>
	<partialresource>
		<resourceid>1672</resourceid>
		<title>NASA Educator Guides</title>
		<description>offer lessons and activities for learning about aeronautics, clouds, energy, the electromagnetic spectrum, the International Space Station, Mars, microgravity, the moon and the Apollo missions, ocean winds, optics (light and color), planetary geology, rainfall, rockets, sun-earth connections, weather, the Wright brothers, and the brain in space.</description>
	</partialresource>
	<partialresource>
		<resourceid>1779</resourceid>
		<title>Online Health Science Curriculum</title>
		<description>provides over 300 interdisciplinary activities designed to help students learn about blood, bones, the brain, cardiovascular system, diabetes, forces and motion, health careers, hearing, levers in the body, nutrition, obesity, oral health, population demographics, the pulmonary system, sleep, stereotypes, and vision.</description>
	</partialresource>
	<partialresource>
		<resourceid>1784</resourceid>
		<title>ScienCentralNews</title>
		<description>provides the latest news on developments in life sciences, physical sciences, and technology. Sort articles by topic -- genetics, animals, the brain, chemistry, physics, earth, oceans, astronomy, climate, engineering, biotechnology, computers, nanotechnology, and others. See articles on cancer causing genes, music for pain, fat vaccine, biofuel energy, no-mow grass, liquid armor, fouled beaches, phones and driving, auto-focus eyewear, activity breaks and memory, and more.</description>
	</partialresource>
	<partialresource>
		<resourceid>1785</resourceid>
		<title>Neuroscience for Kids</title>
		<description>explores the brain and nervous system. Learn about brain development, brain lobes, the cerebral cortex, the skull, blood supply, brain fitness, neurons, the autonomic nervous system, sensory systems, the spinal cord, laughter and the brain, the musical brain, face recognition, drug effects, neurological and mental disorders, and more.</description>
	</partialresource>
	<partialresource>
		<resourceid>1916</resourceid>
		<title>Memory</title>
		<description>dissects a sheep brain to show us "the anatomy of memory." See works of an artist who paints entirely from memory. (Compare his paintings to photos of places.) Play interactive games that test your memory -- learn ways to improve it. Discover why some things are easier to remember than others (droodles game). Which facial features help us remember a face? Which image of the penny is correct? Try a mnemonic device called "elaborative encoding."</description>
	</partialresource>
	<partialresource>
		<resourceid>1939</resourceid>
		<title>Science of Mental Illness</title>
		<description>provides six lessons that help students understand what mental illnesses are. PET images show changes in the brain and how treatment can change activity levels and restore functioning. Case studies and other activities explore differences among illnesses, risk factors, and treatment plan goals. Students develop a brochure to inform people about mental illness.</description>
	</partialresource>
	<partialresource>
		<resourceid>1948</resourceid>
		<title>How Your Brain Understands What Your Ear Hears</title>
		<description>helps students learn how audio and visual cues can help communication, how loudness is measured, how changes in the "hearing pathway" may affect hearing, and how to prevent hearing loss. Animations (under "student activities") show an ear hearing the Gettysburg Address in 5 languages, a graphic display of pitch and volume, and how sounds are converted into electrical impulses and sent to the brain.</description>
	</partialresource>
	<partialresource>
		<resourceid>1954</resourceid>
		<title>Brain: Our Sense of Self</title>
		<description>helps middle school students understand basic scientific principles related to the brain and nervous system. Five lessons examine the structure and specialized regions of the brain, its diverse functions, how the body receives and delivers information through the nervous system, factors that affect learning, and our sense of self. Interactive web activities are included.</description>
	</partialresource>
	<partialresource>
		<resourceid>2056</resourceid>
		<title>Encouraging Girls in Math and Science</title>
		<description>offers tools for teachers to help girls achieve at the same level as boys in math and science. The site is based on five research-based recommendations: teach students that the brain grows when they practice and learn; provide prescriptive, informational feedback on strategies and effort; show female role models; spark initial curiosity and foster long-term interest in math and science; and teach spatial skills.</description>
	</partialresource>
	<partialresource>
		<resourceid>2070</resourceid>
		<title>Digging for Answers</title>
		<description>offers interactive quizzes that draw interesting historical facts from the Smithsonian's collections. Topics include dogs, horses, insects, stars, famous women, clothes, food, brain teasers, and more.</description>
	</partialresource>
	<partialresource>
		<resourceid>2088</resourceid>
		<title>Science Bulletins</title>
		<description>provides visualizations and stories of recentdevelopments in earth science, climate change, biodiversity, humanbiology, evolution, and astrophysics. See visualizations for learningabout sea ice changes, coral reefs, desertification in Africa, originsof our moon, Mars, invasive species, undomesticated horses, humanimagination, our genes and geography, cancer's evolutionary tree, facialexpressions, a "wiring diagram" of the brain, human longevity, and more.</description>
	</partialresource>
	<partialresource>
		<resourceid>2099</resourceid>
		<title>Brain Anatomy</title>
		<description>explores major areas of the brain using this 3-dimensional model.</description>
	</partialresource>
	<partialresource>
		<resourceid>2144</resourceid>
		<title>NIDA for Teens: The Science Behind Drug Abuse</title>
		<description>provides teacher guides, videos, quizzes, and games to help teachers integrate the science behind drug abuse into class activities. Students can read the Sara Bellum Blog to learn about the effects of drugs on the brain and body, and then join a discussion with scientists, science writers, public health analysts, and other students.</description>
	</partialresource>
</result>
